<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://geekkid1.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://geekkid1.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-05-13T19:47:14+00:00</updated><id>https://geekkid1.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, professional website for a recent college graduate. Thank you to github user alshedivat for the template. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">looking forward</title><link href="https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/future/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="looking forward"/><published>2025-05-13T09:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-13T09:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/future</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/future/"><![CDATA[<p>As I write this post I am waiting outside a classroom at the university that I attend, as prepared as I can reasonably expect to be for the <em>very last</em> final exam that I have before I graduate. It’s something that I had stressed over the last few days. It’s the last obstacle before I recieve my Bachelor’s Degree, after all. But I’m prepared. I’ve done well in this class so far, and I’m going to succeed.</p> <p>Even so, though, I think I would do well looking forward, past today, to think about what comes next. Because, after all, I have to keep moving forward.</p> <p>I have a few job applications pending, but they’ve been waiting for quite a while. If I’m being honest, the job market is atrocious in my area at the moment. Every software development related job is one of three things: a senior position I don’t qualify for because I don’t have enough experience, a position that requires a security clearance that I do not have, or a job that I have <em>already applied for</em>. Even so, there’s a few remote jobs I’m waiting on, as well as some jobs that are a little bit less related to my field of study that I’ve more recenty applied to.</p> <p>I’m not all that optimistic, that’s just the way I am, but I am hopeful. Because no matter what happens tomorrow, if I keep trying, I’ll make it eventually. So I have to keep trying.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="musings"/><category term="important"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking about the future as I prepare to graduate.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">an unfamiliar blog</title><link href="https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/anew/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="an unfamiliar blog"/><published>2025-05-05T17:35:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-05T17:35:00+00:00</updated><id>https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/anew</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://geekkid1.github.io/pages/2025/anew/"><![CDATA[<p>Until I get the hang of using this template and this jekyll theme and all that, I am going to leave the previous posts up. But just know, this is the <em>very first post</em> written by me. Anything else that’s written before this post was <em>not</em> written by me.</p> <p>If there are no posts before this post in the blog section, nevermind carry on that just means that I didn’t remove this post when I removed all the ones that I did not write.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="musings"/><category term="important"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first actual post on this blog.]]></summary></entry></feed>